<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changelog on</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in Changelog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 0.23.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-23-0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:01:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-23-0/</guid><description>Version 23 is a big feature update, and v24 is already under way!
Here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s new:
Right to left support Deepdwn now has support for right to left script, both while editing and in the preview.
First, there&amp;rsquo;s a new setting under Preferences-&amp;gt;Input, which controls the default writing and display direction for documents.
Here, you can select Right-to-left, Left-to-right, or Automatic.
If you select right-to-left, or left-to-right, that direction will be used for all documents unless overridden per-document.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.22.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-22-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 13:01:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-22-0/</guid><description>Preferences The preferences UI has gotten a little overhaul
The preferences user interface has been split into multiple sections instead of one long list of settings. The automatic names used for the accent colors in the preference panels have been replaced with a subset of the XKCD color survey colors Color and font preset pickers have been replaced with dropdown selectors Preview font A font selector has been added in preferences for the preview window font.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.21.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-21-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:23:01 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-21-0/</guid><description>Font improvements A couple of features have been added to improve Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s font handling.
Fira Code Fira Code has been added to Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s font list. Fira Code distinguishes itself with its ligature support, groups of two or more characters combined to make a single character.
While these are largely intended for programming, they suit markdown editing as well. A full list of ligatures can be found on the Fira Code github page.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.20.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-20-0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:23:01 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-20-0/</guid><description>This update brings a couple of long overdue features, alongside some bells and whistles.
Local image handling Deepdwn can now display images from your local machine. Both absolute paths, and paths relative to the current document are supported. Setting an image directory via yaml frontmatter may be supported later.
For example:
![A Happy goat!](/home/myname/pictures/goat.jpg) ![A Happy goat!](../goat.jpg) ![A Happy goat!](C:\Users\MyName\Pictures\goat.jpg) Note that paths with spaces in them are not supported in markdown, so you&amp;rsquo;ll either want to replace these with URL escaped space characters %20, ex:</description></item><item><title>Version 0.19.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-19-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:23:01 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-19-0/</guid><description>List continuation When typing a list, pressing enter/return will now insert a new list item at the same indentation level. This works for check lists as well. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want that item, just press enter again.
Center and Highlight Paragraphs can now be centered with -&amp;gt;text&amp;lt;-.
Deepdwn now also supports highlighting text with ==text==.
The code for this in the editor and preview is not identical, so you may see some slight differences in behavior between the two for some edge cases.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.18.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-18-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 17:00:16 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-18-0/</guid><description>This update brings a number of changes to improve Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s accessibility, particularly for keyboard-only and screen reader users.
I need to stress that I&amp;rsquo;m not an accessibility expert, and these changes represent a work in progress for accessibility in Deepdwn. If you have specific suggestions in this area, or something isn&amp;rsquo;t working for you that really ought to be, please reach out and let me know and I will try to fix it.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.17.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-17-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 21:42:20 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-17-0/</guid><description>The big update I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to launch this update, there&amp;rsquo;s some good stuff in here.
New name and branding First, JotDown has been renamed to Deepdwn. There are a couple of reasons for this, but mostly it should be much easier to find by name. (Project downloads may still be called JotDown.zip for a bit)
The Itch.io page has been updated with a spiffy new design to help highlight features, and the app has a new icon.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.14.2</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-14-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 17:55:02 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-14-2/</guid><description>This update brings a few features to improve usability when managing more files.
File list updates The file list now has a search field! This will search all (currently visible, subject to tag/category/folder filtering) files, based on their content or filename.
The file list now shows the currently selected folder or tag or category in the heading at the top to help make it more obvious that you&amp;rsquo;re looking at a filtered set of files.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.13.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-13-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 17:49:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-13-0/</guid><description>Ascii Tabs JotDown now supports guitar tabs in the (much more common) ascii tab format. These are properly syntax highlighted in the editor like the other musical formats. An example has been added to the Show Me an Example document.
Minor features More mellow and more attractive editor colors in dark mode. When a syntax error causes a chart or ascii tab blocks not to render, a warning icon will appear in the preview window, with more details when you hover over it.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.12.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-12-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 17:46:21 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-12-0/</guid><description>This update adds a bunch of stuff!
Find and Replace This and UI scaling are the two most important features I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to add. It (hopefully) works the way you&amp;rsquo;d expect.
UI Scaling / Font Size You can now scale all text and UI together using the View menu, or the Ctrl/Cmd + Mousewheel. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a screenshot for this but you can move your head closer and further from the screenshot above to simulate it.</description></item></channel></rss>