<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changelog on</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in Changelog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 0.33.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-33-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 11:54:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-33-0/</guid><description>Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s previous feature update added markdown format checks, and with this update it can fix many of them automatically!
Fix markdown formatting errors When Deepdwn knows how to fix a formatting issue, you can click the format warning icon to show a menu of available fixes.
You can also fix all document errors at once with from the &amp;ldquo;Fix all formatting errors&amp;rdquo; item in the Tools menu. You can even apply fixes to your files automatically on save with &amp;ldquo;Fix formatting issues on save&amp;rdquo; setting in Preferences &amp;gt; Advanced.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.32.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-32-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:18:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-32-1/</guid><description>Quick bugfix release for drafts not appearing in the files panel.
Tweaks Minimum window dimension has been increased to a more realistic size. Still small though. Bug fixes Fixed draft files not appearing when selecting drafts in the filters panel</description></item><item><title>Version 0.32.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-32-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 12:06:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-32-0/</guid><description>Most of this release was focused on small performance changes, but there&amp;rsquo;s one new feature for you!
Markdown format checking Deepdwn can now check your documents for formatting consistency and errors with MarkdownLint.
Deepdwn can warn you if:
Your headings end with punctuation You reversed the parentheses and brackets in your links Your numbered lists are out of order You have trailing spaces after your text And a ton of other things.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.31.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-31-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 20:40:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-31-0/</guid><description>Paste rich text to markdown When you paste HTML content into Deepdwn (copied from a webpage or online document editing tool), Deepdwn will now do its very best to convert it into markdown. This can be a huge time saver when importing formatted content and tables especially.
As a side effect, Deepdwn now supports copy/pasting spreadsheet data directly from Google Sheets, LibreOffice, and Office 365. Others may or may not work!</description></item><item><title>Version 0.30.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-30-0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 12:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-30-0/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a handful of features, changes and bugfixes for you with 0.30!
Multiple tag selection You can now select multiple tags in the filters panel by holding control while clicking them, to further filter your files.
When multiple tags are selected, only files containing all of the selected tags will be visible in the file list.
While you can still only select one category or folder at a time (since a file can only be in a single category or folder), you can now select a category and a folder and one or more tags at the same time to locate files which match all of those criteria.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.29.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-29-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 16:54:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-29-0/</guid><description>Markdown templates Do you find yourself starting documents the same way over and over? Maybe you use the same set of categories or tags, maybe you always add the current date to your blog posts, or maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t like copying YAML every time.
Deepdwn now supports markdown templates to save you a couple of steps.
To create a new template, simply add the tag template to a document&amp;rsquo;s frontmatter, and it will appear in the New File From Template entry in the File menu, or select it from the new drop down next to the New File button in the top bar.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.28.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 21:12:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-1/</guid><description>Quick bugfix release!
Bugfixes Fixed timing issue that caused an error error on some systems when saving files for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.28.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 12:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-0/</guid><description>This update contains a number of smaller display improvements and tweaks. Enjoy!
Display updates In a new feature I&amp;rsquo;m creatively calling &amp;ldquo;Big Headings&amp;rdquo;, Deepdwn can now display your markdown headings, uh, bigger.
Because this is much less compact, and may not be desirable for all users, it can be disabled in the Appearance section in preferences.
The appearance of inline code and code blocks have also been updated, and now more closely match their preview-rendered counterparts.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.27.2</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 19:09:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-2/</guid><description>Bug fixes Fix PDF export only including first page of content for longer documents Fix PDF export missing images under some network conditions</description></item><item><title>Version 0.27.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-1/</guid><description>Bug fixes Fix save command failing when called from shortcut key or file menu. Autosave, Save As, and saving when the editor is focused were not affected Fix wrong color surrounding the close button in the check for updates dialog</description></item></channel></rss>