<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changelog on</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in Changelog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 0.29.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-29-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 12:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-29-0/</guid><description>Markdown templates Do you find yourself starting documents the same way over and over? Maybe you use the same set of categories or tags, maybe you always add the current date to your blog posts, or maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t like copying YAML every time.
Deepdwn now supports markdown templates, to save you a couple of steps.
To create a new template, simply add the tag template to a document&amp;rsquo;s frontmatter, and it will appear in the New File From Template entry in the File menu, or select it from the new drop down next to the New File button in the top bar.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.28.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 21:12:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-1/</guid><description>Quick bugfix release!
Bugfixes Fixed timing issue that caused an error error on some systems when saving files for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.28.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 12:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-28-0/</guid><description>This update contains a number of smaller display improvements and tweaks. Enjoy!
Display updates In a new feature I&amp;rsquo;m creatively calling &amp;ldquo;Big Headings&amp;rdquo;, Deepdwn can now display your markdown headings, uh, bigger.
Because this is much less compact, and may not be desirable for all users, it can be disabled in the Appearance section in preferences.
The appearance of inline code and code blocks have also been updated, and now more closely match their preview-rendered counterparts.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.27.2</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 19:09:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-2/</guid><description>Bug fixes Fix PDF export only including first page of content for longer documents Fix PDF export missing images under some network conditions</description></item><item><title>Version 0.27.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-1/</guid><description>Bug fixes Fix save command failing when called from shortcut key or file menu. Autosave, Save As, and saving when the editor is focused were not affected Fix wrong color surrounding the close button in the check for updates dialog</description></item><item><title>Version 0.27.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 11:00:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-27-0/</guid><description>Word count statistics Deepdwn can now track and display your word count over time in pretty charts by year, month and day. The global/file button switches between showing your word count updates for the current file, or all the files you&amp;rsquo;ve edited, combined.
Year view Month view Day view There are some other features I&amp;rsquo;d like to add to this in the future, like word count goals, and configuring for the time the day starts and ends</description></item><item><title>Version 0.26.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-26-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 16:36:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-26-0/</guid><description>Live tables Verion 0.26 brings a shiny new table editor to Deepdwn!
Tables are realigned automatically while editing. You can press tab (and shift tab) to jump between columns, or press enter to move to the next row.
You can find the shortcuts for adding, removing, sorting, and moving columns and rows here: Shortcuts. Most of these are also available when using vim or emacs shortcuts as well.
Adding and removing columns In addition to the more explicit shortcuts above, new columns can be added by typing a pipe character ( | ) in an existing table cell.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.25.3</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 23:25:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-3/</guid><description>Quick bugfix release for spell checking issues!
Bugfixes Fixed spellcheck context menu offering no suggestions for misspelled words Fixed spellcheck failing to save changes when cursor wasn&amp;rsquo;t already on misspelled word.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.25.2</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 11:12:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-2/</guid><description>More improvements for markdown folding!
Tweaks Added shortcuts for folding specific heading levels for sublime and emacs key bindings. Added toggle fold command for default key bindings Cursor can now move past fold markers without clearing them Prevent folding when no lines would be folded. Deleting a fold marker (via delete key) now unfolds the content instead of deleting whole region, similar to backspace key. Unfold and toggle fold commands now work when used on unfolded content that follows a fold marker, even if that content is technically on a different line.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.25.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 19:17:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-1/</guid><description>Quick bugfix update for some issues related to key shortcuts for markdown folding
Also added a couple of additional key shortcuts for folding
Bugfixes Fixed sections unfolding immediately after edit Fixed section folding not persisting between document loads Fixed sections without any content not folding correctly</description></item></channel></rss>