<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changelog on</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in Changelog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 0.25.2</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 11:12:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-2/</guid><description>More improvements for markdown folding!
Tweaks Added shortcuts for folding specific heading levels for sublime and emacs key bindings. Added toggle fold command for default key bindings Cursor can now move past fold markers without clearing them Prevent folding when no lines would be folded. Deleting a fold marker (via delete key) now unfolds the content instead of deleting whole region, similar to backspace key. Unfold and toggle fold commands now work when used on unfolded content that follows a fold marker, even if that content is technically on a different line.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.25.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 19:17:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-1/</guid><description>Quick bugfix update for some issues related to key shortcuts for markdown folding
Also added a couple of additional key shortcuts for folding
Bugfixes Fixed sections unfolding immediately after edit Fixed section folding not persisting between document loads Fixed sections without any content not folding correctly</description></item><item><title>Version 0.25.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:12:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-25-0/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s another big update that I had planned to be a small update instead. I hope you like features!
Document folding Deepdwn now supports persistent document folding.
-
With this change, you can collapse entire sections of your markdown documents based on heading level.
Any heading ending in ... (three periods) is considered &amp;ldquo;folded&amp;rdquo; and will remain folded, even when the file is saved and reopened again later.
To unfold a heading you can:</description></item><item><title>Version 0.24.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-24-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 11:30:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-24-1/</guid><description>Minor bug fix release only
Bug fixes Fix missing local images in PDF exports</description></item><item><title>Version 0.24.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-24-0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 18:01:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-24-0/</guid><description>Update 0.24 is a feature-packed update that I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking forward to for a while.
Document linking First up, document linking! This is really a collection of features, so let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.
Deepdwn now supports links from one document to another, both in the editor and preview window.
This is done using the standard markdown link format:
[My Document](../my_document.md) Clicking this link in the preview window, or control-clicking the filename portion of the link in the editor, will both take you directly to the file.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.23.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-23-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:36:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-23-1/</guid><description>Quick bugfix release this time
Bugfixes Fix selecting &amp;ldquo;Save as&amp;rdquo; from the file menu not doing anything. Right-clicking files and selecting &amp;ldquo;Save As&amp;rdquo; in the file list is unaffected by this bug. Removed double confirmation when attempting to save file that will overwrite an existing file.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.23.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-23-0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:01:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-23-0/</guid><description>Version 23 is a big feature update, and v24 is already under way!
Here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s new:
Right to left support Deepdwn now has support for right to left script, both while editing and in the preview.
First, there&amp;rsquo;s a new setting under Preferences-&amp;gt;Input, which controls the default writing and display direction for documents.
Here, you can select Right-to-left, Left-to-right, or Automatic.
If you select right-to-left, or left-to-right, that direction will be used for all documents unless overridden per-document.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.22.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-22-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 13:01:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-22-0/</guid><description>Preferences The preferences UI has gotten a little overhaul
The preferences user interface has been split into multiple sections instead of one long list of settings. The automatic names used for the accent colors in the preference panels have been replaced with a subset of the XKCD color survey colors Color and font preset pickers have been replaced with dropdown selectors Preview font A font selector has been added in preferences for the preview window font.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.21.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-21-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:23:01 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-21-0/</guid><description>Font improvements A couple of features have been added to improve Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s font handling.
Fira Code Fira Code has been added to Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s font list. Fira Code distinguishes itself with its ligature support, groups of two or more characters combined to make a single character.
While these are largely intended for programming, they suit markdown editing as well. A full list of ligatures can be found on the Fira Code github page.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.20.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-20-0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:23:01 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-20-0/</guid><description>This update brings a couple of long overdue features, alongside some bells and whistles.
Local image handling Deepdwn can now display images from your local machine. Both absolute paths, and paths relative to the current document are supported. Setting an image directory via yaml frontmatter may be supported later.
For example:
![A Happy goat!](/home/myname/pictures/goat.jpg) ![A Happy goat!](../goat.jpg) ![A Happy goat!](C:\Users\MyName\Pictures\goat.jpg) Note that paths with spaces in them are not supported in markdown, so you&amp;rsquo;ll either want to replace these with URL escaped space characters %20, ex:</description></item></channel></rss>