<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changelog on</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in Changelog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 0.39.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-39-0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:40:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-39-0/</guid><description>Welcome to a small quite large update that got out way out of hand
Fountain First, Deepdwn now supports the Fountain screenplay format: https://fountain.io/
Fountain is a plain-text, human-readable format for writing and sharing screenplays. It has a lot in common with markdown, and is a good fit for Deepdwn.
You can create a new Fountain document in several ways:
Select File &amp;gt; New file &amp;gt; Fountain from the application menu or create a new file (which is markdown by default) and save it with the Fountain file extension: my_file.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.38.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-38-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 13:01:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-38-0/</guid><description>New features Mac universal build Deepdwn now provides a universal Mac OS build, supporting both x64 and ARM64 (M1/M2) processors without the need for Rosetta.
This build is larger (since it contains both the X64 and ARM builds combined), but is recommended for users on M1 or M2 macs.
For technical reasons, an ARM-only build is not available right now.
Font lists Deepdwn now shows a proper list of fonts when selecting a custom font for editor or preview display, instead of requiring you to enter them manually.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.37.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-37-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 18:01:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-37-1/</guid><description>This is primarily a bugfix release!
Autocomplete Autocomplete has gotten a small rework. When using autocomplete to link to other markdown files, more files will be considered if the link being autocompleted doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like a relative path.
For example, when autocompleting the following link
[link](my_file all files with names containing my_file will be shown in the autocomplete list, including those in parent or child folders, relative to the current file.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.37.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-37-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 13:01:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-37-0/</guid><description>This is a minor release, but a couple of small features have snuck in anyway.
New stuff Slightly expanded search capabilities
Previously, all file searches in the file list panel were treated as exact phrase searches. Now, you can search for multiple words, in any order, to locate files that have all of those words in either the file name or content, including the YAML header.
To search for an exact phrase (the previous behavior), wrap your search terms in quotes.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.36.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-36-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 16:50:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-36-1/</guid><description>This version adds some fixes and improvements for table rendering and outline scrolling.
As an aside, further large-scale changes are being made to Deepdwn behind the scenes currently, but they won&amp;rsquo;t be in a releasable state for a while yet.
Tables Tables are now rendered with vertical lines between columns in the preview Very wide tables can now be scrolled left and right in the preview window and in styled HTML exports Very wide tables will be scaled down to fit the page in PDF exports Bugfixes Fixed clicking a heading in the outline panel sometimes highlighting the wrong heading afterward, even though the heading would be scrolled to correctly.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.36.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-36-0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:54:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-36-0/</guid><description>This version adds improvements to a couple of existing features: HTML-to-markdown and synchronized scrolling!
HTML Pasting Significant changes have been made to the convert-pasted-HTML-to-markdown feature to support additional elements, and reduce unnecessary escaping.
Support &amp;lt;var&amp;gt; elements, imported as italic Support definition lists, imported using compact syntax Use different escaping mechanisms for code blocks imported from &amp;lt;pre&amp;gt; tags Do not escape HTML in inline code imported from &amp;lt;code&amp;gt; tags When inline code contains a backtick character, use double backticks for the code element Minimize HTML escaping on paste, and specifically unescape some items if escaped in source Ignore inline styles inside of code blocks and inline code Further changes to this feature are planned, especially to escape markdown in pasted content, but other work will be needed first to make this possible.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.35.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-35-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 13:18:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-35-0/</guid><description>Discord status Deepdwn can now update your status in Discord when you have the Discord application running (if you like).
This integration is disabled by default. To enable it, go to the new Preferences &amp;gt; Integrations section, and enable &amp;ldquo;Show Deepdwn activity in Discord&amp;rdquo;.
Here, you can also enable &amp;ldquo;Show current activity&amp;rdquo;, which will display whether you&amp;rsquo;re actively writing (with a long cooldown) or idle.
You can also enable &amp;ldquo;Show current file&amp;rdquo;, disabled by default, which will also display the title or filename of your active document.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.34.0</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-34-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:57:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-34-0/</guid><description>New accessibility preferences A new section has been added to Deepdwn&amp;rsquo;s preferences for accessibility settings. The existing settings for the tab key behavior (toggling between indenting and navigation), and high-contrast display, have both been moved here.
Two new options have been added here as well:
Display entire document at once: By default, Deepdwn hides offscreen content for performance reasons in a way that may interfere with screen readers, in some cases.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.33.2</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-33-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 01:13:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-33-2/</guid><description>Just another quick bugfix and error logging release, while larger updates are being worked on.
Tweaks Additional capturing of otherwise uncaptured errors.
Bug fixes Fix error that could occur while parsing document titles.</description></item><item><title>Version 0.33.1</title><link>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-33-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 13:07:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://support.deepdwn.com/changelog/version-0-33-1/</guid><description>Just a small patch release right now
Tweaks Improved responsiveness of find-in-document Removed extra spacing around highlighted search results Added error logging for unexpected application errors. These are located at: Windows: %appdata%/Deepdwn/logs Mac: ~/Library/Application Support/Deepdwn/logs Linux: ~/.config/Deepdwn/logs</description></item></channel></rss>